你们为什么不出来
Why don't you come on out,
到路上来
join us on the road?
真好
Yeah, that's great.
一开始就很顺利
It's going well right out of the gate.
现在第二步 交出你们的武器
Now, step two… hand over your weapons.
凭什么
Why should we?
因为武器不是你们的
Well, they're not yours.
那是谁的
Whose are they?
你们的财产
Your property…
现在归尼根所有
now belongs to Negan.
如果你们能搞到大卡车
And if you can get your hands on a tanker,
那我们就想跟你们认识认识
you're people our person wants to know.
交出随身武器 好吗
So let's get those sidearms, shall we?
快点
Right now.
谢谢
Thank you.
如果你得吃屎
If you have to eat shit,
最好别细细品味
best not to nibble.
咬 咀嚼 吞咽 重复
Bite, chew, swallow, repeat.
这样更快
It goes quicker.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们是什么人
Who are you people?
我明白你很好奇
I get the curiosity,
但我们也有问题
but we have questions ourselves.
而且要由我们来问问题
And we'll be the ones asking them.
同时我们要送你们回家
while we drive you back to wherever it is you call home.
看看你们在哪儿挂帽子
Take a gander at where you hang your hats.
但先聊聊你们的储备
First, though, your shit.
你们有什么东西
What have you got for us?
你刚拿走了
Yeah, you just took it.
拜托
Come on.
能别装了吗
I mean, can we not, okay?
有更多东西
There's more.
总是有更多东西
There is always more.
T
T…
带我的手下去卡车后面
Take my man to the back of the truck,
从后保险杠里开始
start inside the back bumper,
一直搜到前面
Work your way to the front.
快走
Go.
咬 咀嚼 吞咽 重复
Bite, chew, swallow, repeat.
尼根是谁
Who's Negan?
叮咚 地狱的钟声响起了
Ding, dong, hell's bells.
一般情况下我们自我介绍的方式是
You see, usually we introduce ourselves.
开枪打死你们中的一人
by just popping one of you right off the bat.
但你们看起来像是讲理的人
But you seem like reasonable people.
天啊 你还穿着海军制服呢
I mean, you're sportin' dress blues, for christ's sake.
如我所说 我们要送你们回家
And, like I said, we're gonna drive you back to where you were.
你知道这有多尴尬吗
I mean, do you know how awkward it is.
跟一个你刚杀了他朋友的人拼车
carpooling with someone whose friend or friends you've just killed?
但我跟你们说了 别问问题
But I told you not to ask any questions.
结果这红毛做了什么
And then what does this ginger do?
就这样了
So that's that.
我不想让你们误以为我软弱
I don't want you to get the wrong impression of me.
等等
Wait.
你没必要这样做
You don't have to do this.
闭嘴
Shut up.
我在跟管事的说话
I am talking to the man.
不 你没有
No, you're not.
我不会杀了你们的
I'm not gonna kill you.
等等
Wait, wait.
知道吗
You know what?
我会的
Yes, I am.
那混蛋比看起来要厉害
Son of a bitch was tougher than he looked.
- 他割伤你了吗 - 有点
- Did he cut you? - A little.
真是一群畜生
What a bunch of assholes.
回家去给你包扎
Let's get you fixed up at home.
遵命
Yes, ma'am.
细细品味吧
Nibble on that.
《行尸走肉》
好了 新计划
All right, new plan.
几把枪的照明弹还不够
Flares from a few guns aren't enough.
行尸太多 太分散了
Too many walkers, too spread out.
我们不去武器库了
We're not going to the armory.
我们需要采石场的车子
We need our vehicles back at the quarry.
我们都开车 把它们赶在一起
All of us drive. We'll need to round 'em up.
我们离开 然后回来
We leave, we come back.
好
Okay.
但是朱迪思
But Judith…
去采石场然后回来 我…
To the quarry and back, I…
我带着她
I'll take her.
让她安全待在我的教堂里
Keep her safe in my church.
直到你们引开行尸
until you all lead the walkers away.
你能做到吗
Can you do this?
我应该做到
I'm supposed to.
我必须做到
I have to.
我会做到的
I will.
好吧
All right.
- 带上山姆 - 不行
- Take Sam. - No.
行 山姆 这样更安全
Yes, Sam, it'll be safer.
我不要离开你
I'm not leaving you.
- 山姆 - 妈 我不要
- Sam… - Mom, I'm not.
我能继续
I can keep going.
- 山姆 - 我能继续
- Sam… - I can keep going.
求你了
Please.
我们走吧
Let's just go.
好
Okay.
我会保护好她
I'm going to keep her safe.
谢谢
Thank you.
他能做到的
He's gonna make it.
好吗
Okay?
我知道的
I know it.
山姆
Sam.
我们得试试
We have to try.
我们不能出去 行尸太多了
We cannot go out there. There are too many of them.
罗西塔 他会杀了她的
Rosita, he's gonna kill her.
我们到不了她那里
We won't get to her.
她需要我们
She needs us.
我们会送命的
We'll die.
结果就会是这样
That is what will happen.
我们只有一把枪
We have one gun,
满街都是行尸
and the streets are filled with those things.
那个人需要她
That man needs her.
她是医生 他病了
Okay? She's a doctor. He is sick.
我们都见识过他的生存能力
And I think we've seen that he knows how to survive.
但我们得确保卡萝尔和摩根无恙
But we need to make sure that Carol and Morgan are okay.
然后再作打算
And then we make a plan.
我们不能就这样走了
We cannot just go.
好吧
Okay.
天啊
Oh, god.
罗西塔 我需要你的枪
Rosita, gonna need your gun.
我去褐石房那边检查一下
Gonna do a sweep of the brownstone.
看看还有没有其他隐患
I want to see what other surprises are in here.
他醒了
Hey, he's waking up.
慢点
Easy.
他人呢
Where is he?
丹妮斯人呢
Where's Denise?
他劫持了她 是吧
He took her, didn't he?
我们扶你起来
Let's get you up.
也许他们搜刮这地方时漏掉了一些东西
Maybe when they searched this place, they missed something.
只要搜刮者不是艾登或希斯的小队
Depends if it was Aiden or Heath's group who went through it.
放松
Easy.
圣经也翻一下
Look in the bibles, too.
可能在里面挖了洞
Could've hollowed out the pages.
真的有可能吗
Are you serious?
我们有两颗子弹
We have two bullets.
有人曾在这里避难
People holed up in here.
他们可能会藏枪和弹药
People hide guns, ammo.
或可以点火的东西
Maybe something to start a fire.
天快要黑了 或许我们可以把它们引开
It's getting dark out soon. Maybe we can distract them.
我们需要床单 绳子 毛巾
We need sheets, ropes, towels.
能帮玛姬从另一边爬下来的东西就行
Anything Maggie can use to climb down the other side.
风水轮流转啊
How things turn.
伊妮德
Enid.
我想逃离的时候
When I wanted to run…
你说过 你这样会失去别人
You said, "That's how you lose people…
即使在他们死后
even after they're gone."
这到底是什么意思
What the hell does that mean?
你爱的人
People you love…
他们造就了你
They made you who you are.
他们依然是你的一部分
They're still part of you.
如果你放弃自己
If you stop being you,
他们在你身上留下的造就你的最后痕迹
that last bit of them that's still around inside, who you are…
就会消失
It's gone.
对你来说这些人是谁
Who are those people to you?
我父母
My parents.
一个叫戴尔的人
A man named Dale.
玛姬的父亲 赫谢尔
Maggie's father, Hershel.
一个叫安德莉亚的女人 一个叫泰尔西的男人
A woman named Andrea. A man named Tyreese.
对你来说这些人是谁
Who are they to you?
我的父母
My parents.
那他们就还在这里
Then they're still here…
因为你还在
'cause you're still here.
一旦有缺口
When there's an opening,
我们就冲到塔里
we'll make a break for that tower.
不行 我会拖累你的
No, I'll just slow you down.
丹妮斯
Denise.
丹妮斯 你现在
Denise, you're here…
和我一起
With me.
我需要你
I need you.
也许我想要你在身边
Maybe I want you to stay.
因为我好喜欢有你的陪伴
'cause I'm enjoying your company so much.
你待在这里
I want you to stay put.
什么
What?
我希望你能回来
I wanted you to come back.
我可以应付的
I can handle myself.
- 你说过你需要帮忙 - 不
- You said you wanted help. - No,
我不希望你对这个地方失去信心
I didn't want you to give up on this place,
对这些人失去信心 或是感到害怕
On these people, to be afraid.
你说得对
You were right.
所以我现在在这里
So I'm here now.
我要出去给你帮忙
And I'm going out there and I'm helping you.
我们得把她从高台上救下来
We have to get her off that platform.
她受伤了 需要我们的帮助才能翻过墙
She's hurt. She needs help getting over the wall.
我去爬门 你去引开它们
I can climb up the gate. You can distract them.
我们齐心协力
We do it together.
反正我无论如何都会跟着你
I'm just gonna follow you, anyway.
你继续找那圣经里的手枪吧
You keep looking for the Bible glock…
我去做个东西帮她爬下去
I'll make her something to climb down.
好吧
Okay.
我喜欢你之前说的那句
I like what you said before.
我并非生来如此
That I wasn't born this way.
你说得对
You're right.
我变了
I changed.
现在我要帮你改变
And now I want to help you change.
你说对了
You were right.
我们去救玛姬吧
Let's get Maggie.
- 你就不能老实待这儿吗 - 不能
- Can't you just stay here? - Nope.
这是上天赐予你的礼物 丹妮斯
You've been given a gift, Denise.
你总有一天会明白的
You'll see that one day.
也许不会
Or maybe you won't.
怪物会来抓你
The monsters will come,
它们来抓你时 你跑也跑不掉
And you won't be able to run away when they come for you.
外面那些怪物
The ones out there.
会把你撕个粉碎
And they will tear you apart.
啃个精光 生吞活剥
and eat you up all while you're still alive.
山姆
Sam?
快走 快走
Come on, come on.
- 宝贝 山姆 - 你能行的
- Sweetheart? Sam? - You can do it.
- 你能行的 - 你能行的
- You can do it. - Yes, you can.
山姆 山姆 走了
Sam. Sam, come on.
- 快走 山姆 - 山姆
- Come on, Sam. - Sam.
- 山姆 - 山姆
- Sam? - Sam…
嘿 你可以的
Hey, you can do this.
山姆 看着妈妈
Sam, just look at mom.
亲爱的 你可以的
Honey, you can do it.
山姆 你会被…
Sam, you're gonna get…
山姆 亲爱的 你得跟我来
Sam, honey, I need you to come with me.
- 山姆 - 你得跟我来
- Sam. - I need you to come with me.
- 我也想 - 你要坚强起来
- I want to. - I need you to be strong.
山姆
Sam…
妈妈
Mom!
- 杰茜 - 杰茜 杰茜
- Jessie? - Jessie. Jessie.
- 不 - 杰茜 杰茜
- No. - Jessie. Jessie.
跟我们走
Come with us.
快 我们得走了
Come on. We have to go.
不
No.
爸爸
Dad.
快走
Come on.
你
You.
爸爸
Dad?
卡尔
Carl.
不
No.
我们迟早会杀出一条血路出去
Sooner or later, we're fighting our way out.
- 我知道你心里非常清楚 - 是啊
- I know that you're fully aware that we will. - Yeah…
我们会的
We will.
但不包括你
Not you.
- 在我看来… - 尤金
- Well, by my reckoning… - Eugene.
得了吧
Come on.
它们正在往枪声的地方走
They're moving towards the gunfire.
那声尖叫
That shout.
我估计有些人还以为他们能抵抗一下呢
I suppose someone thought they could put up a fight.
我想你们都是这么想的
I guess you all thought that.
我们的确抵抗了
We did put up a fight.
所以你的朋友们都死了
That's why your friends are dead.
是啊
Yeah.
我们应该再等一等 再观望一会儿
We should've waited and watched a little longer.
我太自私了
I was selfish.
但也许如果我不那么自私
But maybe if I wasn't so selfish,
就根本不会得到救治
I wouldn't have got that IV.
我们得找个缺口出去
We're gonna find a gap a go.
登上那座哨塔 翻到墙的那一边
Up that guard tower and over the wall.
你不用害怕
You don't need to be afraid.
去死吧
Go to hell.
你得知道
You need to know.
在外面远比里面安全
it's safer out there than it is in here.
开始走吧
Start moving.
开始走
现在 直接走到那个护柱下面
Now, straight up that guard post.
千万别停
and do not stop.
走吧
Go.
该死的
Shit!
快走 跟我一起
Let's go. Come with me, now.
你把我送到医务室 我可以救你的命
You get me to the infirmary, I save your life.
我会救你的
I'll save your life.
你曾经有个孩子
You had a child.
对吧
Right?
还有丈夫
A husband?
我之前并非有意伤害你 我只是不得不阻止你
I didn't want to hurt you, I just had to stop you.
你救他是为了你自己 不是为了我们
You saved him for you, not us.
如果是为了我们 你就会…
If it was for us, you would've…
我应该杀了你的
I should've killed you.
我真该那么做的
I should've.
你杀不了
You can't.
医务室就在巷子对面
The infirmary's right across the alley.
我们必须立刻把你弄过去
We need to get you there now.
那个梯子周围没有行尸 我本可以爬上去的
The ladder was clear. Could've made it.
你为了我而回头
You turned back for me.
或许是因为你需要医生
Maybe it was because you needed a doctor,
或许是因为你变了
or maybe you changed.
你准备好了吗
You ready?
走 快走
Come on! Come on!
Go! Go!
快走啊
Go!
快 进来
Come on, come on.
你没事吧
You okay?
我没事 我的病人们怎么样了
I'm fine. How are my patients?
他们挺好的 我们把他们转移到楼上了以防万一
They're doing well. We moved them upstairs just in case.
天啊
Oh, my god.
是那个孩子
It's the kid.
他被咬了吗
Is he bit?
没有
Nope.
怎么了
What?
我需要绷带
I need bandages.
就在水槽边最高层的架子上
Top shelf, next to the sink.
从冰箱里拿两支注射液 干净毛巾越多越好
Two IVs from the fridge and all the clean towels you can find.
亚伦 把轮床推过来
Aaron, grab the gurney.
这是枪伤吗
This is a gunshot?
手枪 近距离射击
Handgun. Close range.
求你救救他
Please save him.
求你了
Please.
那会把行尸引过来的
That's gonna draw them here.
我需要光源
I need light.
米琼恩 拿毛巾来 准备好
Michonne, towel. Hold it here.
我们需要压住伤口
We need to keep pressure on the wound.
我探进去缝合撕裂处
I'll go in and sew up any lacerations.
就是这样 就那里
Just like that, right here.
斯宾塞 我需要那个平盘
Now, Spencer, I need that pan.
就是托盘上的那个 很好
That one on the tray. Good.
我要进行清洗和缝合
I'm going to clean and close this.
米琼恩 我弄到哪儿你就用毛巾跟着擦拭
Michonne, keep following me with the towel.
你要干什么
What… what are you doing?
瑞克
Rick!
- 瑞克在外面 - 坚持住
- Rick's out there. - Hold on.
- 他需要我帮忙 - 再缝一针
- He needs my help. - Just one more suture.
但他在外面
But he's out there.
这是他儿子 给我点时间
This is his son. Give me a second.
他在孤军奋战
He's taking them all on.
- 我们得去帮他 - 什么
- We have to go get him. - What?
我们必须去
We have to.
- 就看这一战了 - 搞定了
- This is it. - Okay, got it.
击退它们 压制它们
Knock 'em away. Drive 'em down.
我们能打败它们
We can beat'em. We can beat'em!
击退它们 就这样
Drive 'em back. That's it.
我们能一起做到
We can do this together!
你能抱着她吗
Will you take her?
当然
Of course.
跟我来 好的
Come with me. Okay, okay.
- 谢谢你 - 没事
- Thank you. - It's okay.
加百利
Gabriel.
你要干什么
What are you doing?
我们一直在一起祈祷
We've been praying… together.
祈祷上帝能拯救我们的小镇
Praying that god will save our town.
我们的祈祷应验了
Well, our prayers have been answered.
上帝会拯救亚历山大
God will save Alexandria…
因为上帝给予了我们拯救自己的勇气
because God has given us the courage to save it ourselves.
前面的尸群散开了
Guys, it's thinning out there in front.
我们得离开这里
We need to get out there.
- 瑞克在进行抵抗 - 怎么抵抗
- Rick's making a stand. - How's that?
他正在外面与米琼恩他们一同战斗
He's out there fighting them with Michonne and some others.
是时候了
It's time.
我要去巷子里
Up the alley. I'm going.
丹妮斯很安全
Denise is safe.
你看到她了吗
Did you see her?
她撑到医务室了
Yeah, she made it to the infirmary.
- 我去帮瑞克 - 我也去
- I'm gonna go help Rick. - I'm going, too.
- 我跟你一起 - 那好 我也去
- I'm with you. - All right, me, too.
- 我跟着你 - 尤金 你不必这么做
- Right behind you. - Eugene, you don't have to.
这不对 我必须这么做
That's incorrect. I do.
今天没人能置身事外
No one gets to clock out today.
该死 今天的事将被载入史册
And, hell, this is a story people are gonna tell.
这边 快点
This way! Come on!
抱歉
I'm sorry.
不
No.
去帮她
Go get her!
来这边
Over here!
快点 这边
Come on, here!
- 来这边 - 格伦
- Over here! - Glenn!
不 格伦
No! Glenn!
- 格伦 - 过来 来这边 过来啊
- Glenn! - Come on! Over here, come on!
玛姬
Maggie!
伊妮德
Enid!
这边 这边 过来啊
Over here! Over here, come on.
快点
Come on!
快走 快翻过去
Just go! Just get over!
- 快走 - 不
- Go! - No!
快走
Go!
快点
Come on!
该死
Shit.
- 不 格伦 - 快走
- No, Glenn! - Go!
来这边
Over here!
格伦
Glenn!
你能把门打开吗
Can you get the gate?
谢谢 伙计
Appreciate it, pal.
来吧 我们拉你
Come on, we got you.
发生了什么
What the hell happened?
我不知道 我刚回来
I don't know. I just got back.
听着
Listen…
我们可以引开一部分行尸
We can… we can lead some of them away,
但是它们很分散
but they're scattered.
不 我们一网打尽
No, we get 'em all together.
不用引开它们
Won't have to lead 'em away.
移动 后退
Move it! Back up!
好 可以了
All right, that's it!
别松懈
Don't let up!
我错了
I was wrong.
我以为在墙内生活了这么久
I thought after living behind these walls for so long that…
也许他们学不会了
Maybe they couldn't learn.
但是今天
But today…
我看到了他们能做什么
I saw what they could do,
我们能做什么
What we could do,
如果我们一起合作
If we work together.
就可以重建这些墙
We'll rebuild the walls.
扩建这些墙
We'll expand the walls.
会有希望的 一定会有的
There will be more. There's gotta be more.
迪安娜说的一切
Everything Deanna was talking about…
都有可能
Is possible.
全都有可能 我现在明白了
It's all possible. I see that now.
当我在外面
When I was out there…
和他们在一起时
With them…
当这一切结束
When it was over…
我们重新夺回这个地方时
When I knew we had this place again…
我心中有一种感觉
I had this feeling.
我花了一段时间
It took me a while.
才想起来那感觉是什么
To remember what it was…
因为自从我在医院醒来后
Because I haven't felt it.
就再没有过那种感觉了
Since before I woke up in that hospital bed.
我想让你看看新世界 卡尔
I want to show you the new world, Carl.
我想为你使之成为现实
I want to make it a reality for you.
求你了 卡尔
Please, Carl…
让我给你看看吧
Let me show you.
求你了 儿子 别死
Plea… please, son, don't die.